http://www.icvolunteers.org/privacy

EN | FR | ES
Home VolunteeringOpportunities for Individual VolunteersCyberVolunteeringOur Volunteer CharterFAQ for VolunteersGlossary of terms ServicesOur ServicesConference ServicesCyberVolunteeringCulture & LanguagesCommunications and JournalismSocial ResearchCorporate MentoringFAQ: Who can use our services? ProjectsWhat's happening?Short Term ProjectsLong Term ProjectsJobs / InternshipsProjects by InterestCalendarLinks and Resources NewsNewsVideosPerspectivesPress ReleasesPress ArticlesPublications About UsWho are we?Network & BeneficariesOfficesSome History...Managing BoardPartnersDonorsAffiliations ContactContact usOur officesSign up to volunteerVolunteer conditions Register
Site policy for ICV
Your personal information - We do not collect personal information such as email addresses or telephone numbers unless you specifically provide it to us through a form. ICVolunteers will not share, sell, publish or otherwise divulge your information --including your email address-- with third parties, without your permission. Anti-spam - This site has security measures against automatic email harvesting, a major source of email addresses used for nefarious purposes. Information automatically logged - We may use your IP address --or number that identifies your server-- to help to diagnose problems with our own server, to administer our web site, and to gather general statistical information. These statistics include no personally identifying information. Cookies - 'Cookies' are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our site uses cookies only to keep track of your sign in name and to keep you signed in once you have entered your password. Security - This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We regularly perform routine security analyses on all databases and procedures to ensure the security of information. External links - This site may contain links to other sites. ICVolunteers is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Your consent - By submitting information, you permit ICVolunteers to collect and use this information. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page. You will always be aware of the information we collect, how we intend to use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Data quality/access - This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: You can visit the following URL: www.icvolunteers.org You can send email to info@icvolunteers.org Reuse Policy - The viewpoints and opinions expressed, unless otherwise noted, do not necessarily reflect the views of ICVolunteers. Generally, the contents from public pages may be reproduced if clear and precise credit to the writer is given, and reference to this site is indicated (www.icvolunteers.org). However, content may be copyrighted to one or more authors. If in doubt, contact ICVolunteers. Questions / Contact - If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact ICVolunteers at: ICVolunteers, PO Box 755, 1211 Geneva, Switzerland. Phone: +41 (0) 22 800 14 36 / Fax: +41 (0) 22 800 14 37 Email: info@icvolunteers.org Technical Issues - If you need help, please do not hesitate to contact support@icvolunteers.org.
Home|Volunteering|Services|Projects|News|About Us|Contact|Register|MyICV ©1998-2020 ICVolunteers|design + programming mcart group|Updated: 2019-01-28 10:52 GMT|Privacy|Admin
